No living was harmed during the
production of this series.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com
Let my children go take me.
No!
I healed your disabled son!
I wanted you beside me.
But you stood against me!
You will pay the price with his life.
Stop!
Stop.
They are young.
They can...
They can obey.
You will spare their lives now.
Take my life.
Take my life. Or else...
...I will try beheading you
even in my last breath!
Come on. Take me.
Take me, so the frontiers will be yours.
My children will go to Yenisehir with Boran.
And you will cut my head off.
What do I..
..have left...
...but to die on this way anyway?
Osman, the man who convinced the...
...shepherd Turks...
...Osman who ignited the fire...
..of the dawah (case) in their hearts.
Let his children live..
...so they can be our slaves.
Nayman.
They can only be slaves!
My children..
I will put your head on the tip of my spear...
...and visit all the tribes, Osman.
It's over!
I will say that
they are all my slaves.
Come. Come.
Archers.
Why should I let the children live...
...and give them a chance to take revenge, Nayman?
Kill them!
O Haqq!
We arrived, Osman Bey!
-My children... Are you alright?
-We are alright, father.
My children... Take my children away!
Hang on, Osman Bey.
-This way...
-O Allah..
Ya Allah.
Osman
Where are you going, Osman?!
I will cut your children's heads off...
...and give them to their mothers!
Do not let them escape!
This forest is mine!
Catch them
There are no traces here.
We won't stop before we find Osman Bey, Alps.
There is blood on the ground.
Traces lead this way.
The blood is fresh. Let's go now, brothers!
Let's leave a trace..
...so if someone comes for help, they can find us.
Come on brothers, let's go now!
Thank you, Salur Bey. Thank you.
My children.. Are you alright?
We are going to Salur Bey's tribe.
But we will not use the main road...
...since we attacked them from north...
...now we have to go from the west.
We will build a line of defense there.
Come on Alps.
Split! Go everywhere! So...
...they cannot follow us.
Where did you go, Osman?
You will find Osman right now! Split!
I can smell Osman's blood
from somewhere close, Lord.
They are close.
My Lord. We found him.
One trace shows this way the other leads to Aksu.
They parted their ways to split our power.
The one who leaves the herd gets caught by a wolf.
Now they are cornered.
Go into the woods and bring me his head!
Not only have I settled in there...
...I am now at Nayman's service.
Good.
So you gained Nayman's trust.
I am as close to him as his helper Tendu.
Good.
Then we will have this thing done tonight, Ayceren.
You will take that seal from Nayman.
First, the army that gathered
behind Nayman will leave him...
...then his head will leave his body.
Yenisehir
Osman Bey's mansion.
My flower.
I was afraid that something
would happen to you.
I was afraid as well.
I was afraid that I wouldn't be
able to protect our child.
However, I knew you would come.
You keep your promise.
Our child.
-We will have a child.
-Yes.
I wanted to tell you the news personally,
however..
It was not in our destiny.
It's alright my flower.
You can give me the news next time.
And..
I think it will be a girl.
She will look like her mother.
She will be a brave one like her mother.
No, I don't think so.
I think it will be a brave boy like his father, Aktemur.
Alcicek..
You gave me the world.
And Allah granted me with you.
Don't take these off again, alright?
Let me go and check.
ueiuso
Tell me, where is Osman?
Where is he, what happened
Alps!
Bring your swords,
send word to sisters and bring the horses.
Iltutan wouldn't leave Osman,
they are in trouble.
Malhun went to check the bazaar
quickly send word Bengi Hatun.
-Everyone is in your hands.
-Don't worry, come on.
Aunt.
-I will come with you.
-Quickly.
My valiant, let's go. Bring the horses!
Quickly.
Alps, bring my armor.
Give me.
Iltutan, let's go my valiant.
Take us to Osman our children.
Quickly, quickly!
Salur Bey is coming
-There are woundeds!
-Thank you, Salur Bey.
- You host us in your tents.
- Of course, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey is here.
Hear me out people! Be prepared!
There are woundeds!
Find the healers quickly!
People!
Gather around!
Quickly, I told you..
We came, however,
we brought trouble with us.
What will we do, Bey?
Now, everyone will form a defence line.
Salur Bey.
Now, you will bring me..
All the bows, arrows and swords you have.
Now, this place is not a tribe..
-It is Turks' last castle.
-As you wish, Bey.
Quickly!
Come on, faster!
Archers, gather around
Bring all the shields, quickly!
Close the doors!
Murat..
Where to?
You said that the ones who can
hold sword could join you, Osman Bey.
I can hold a sword.
No...
No way.
We fall to the ground for you.
My son.
No!
You will grow up,
you will become a valiant.
After that,
you will clash like a valiant with us.
For Allah's sake.
Come on now, get back to your tent.
Alright, son? Alps, look here!
-Take this kid.
-As you command.
Come on my son, come on..
Bring fire, Alps
Bring the healers quickly!
Bring fire!
The tracks..
Lead to a little tribe, my Lord.
They've sheltered in the tribe.
They've sheltered in their own graves.
We will burn down the tribe,
and let their blood flow, Lord.
Nokers!
Burn down the tribe that sheltered Osman.
Hang their heads on pikes.
Quickly!
Stop, Nayman
I won't let Osman get away again.
If Osman is sheltered in the tribe,
he must have a trick up his sleeve.
I will wait for soldiers
scattered around the forest to come.
And then, I will destroy that tribe.
Osman is in our claws, Lord.
Osman's fate is death.
Osman will not escape his fate anymore.
Come on! Come on, people!
Faster!
My Bey, let me cauterize it.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate. O Healer!
the merciful, the compassionate. Come on, Boran.
Come on.
You'll be alright my Bey.
I'm good.
No! Alps!
Don't close the entrance!
If we close, they will try to destroy it.
But if we leave a narrow entrance, they will enter.
In a narrow place, numbers don't matter.
We'll be equal.
Salur Bey, where is the Greek Fire
that we gave you?
That way, Orhan Bey.
What is it, son?
My Bey, we'll hold the narrow passage
as long as we can.
When we are out of strength...
...they will burn in our fire.
The fire of our rage.
EyvAllah, son.
EyvAllah.
-With your permission, father.
-Go ahead.
Go ahead.
We'll defend this place.
-We'll defend it somehow.
-We will, my Bey.
Great effort you're showing. Thank you.
Thank you.
You didn't say our tribe was small...
...but you armed us and gave us
the Greek fire.
Now I see why you did, Osman Bey.
EyvAllah, Salur Bey.
EyvAllah.
We won't leave this place. We won't.
We will defend it for sure.
We'll defend it for sure.
Come, dastards.
This is the last fortress of Turks.
You won't be able to pass.
Come. Just come.
Trails here!
Kayi sign.
This way! Come on!
Come on, Orhan.
Come on, son.
Come on, son. Come on. Come, come.
Come. Jump in.
Come.
Come here, vile dogs!
Osman
Instead of dying alone in the woods
..you took shelter in this tribe.
This will just increase the number of people
who are going to die with you.
We'll see.
You can't run anymore, Osman
I thought you were a brave man.
People in the tribe!
You don't have to die with Osman.
Just give him to me and I will spare your lives.
Delivering Osman Bey would be...
...delivering the freedom of Turks!
Osman Bey is the hope of Turks!
-We won't deliver Osman Bey!
-Osman Bey is the hope of Turks!
This is the land of Turks.
Do your best.
We won't fall easily.
We won't fall easily!
I just gave you a chance.
Dying all together...
...is your choice!
Just come and try, Lord
We will die but not deliver Osman Bey!
Come!
Just come. Sons.
Salur Bey.
People! We won't fall easily!
Attack!
Wait.
Now!
Allah is the greatest!
Shield wall!
O Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Ya Haqq!
-O Allah!
-Allah is the greatest!
They found the trails we put.
Any news from Osman Bey? Where is he?
We're looking for him too, Bala Hatun.
-Trails show this way.
-What trails?
Bala Hatun.
There was blood on the ground.
What are we going to do now, Bala Hatun?
The nearest place is Salur Tribe.
They must have taken shelter there.
We're going there. Come on.
Allah is the greatest!
Ya Allah
We're out of arrows, my Bey.
We can't hold much longer.
Now it's time, father.
Just wait. Get prepared.
They're out of arrows.
Attack!
Now!
Ya Haqq!
What a hopeless attempt to survive!
Whatever he does
...both Osman and his sons are going to die today.
My Bey, more are coming. What are we going to do?
-We have nothing left to do, father.
-Well, sons.
Today, we're going to die here or...
...or this place will remain as a land of Turks!
Not every son finds a chance to
become martyr with his father.
I'm happy.
Final destination is martyrdom, father. Now or later.
-Together, InshaAllah.
-Together, sons.
Together, people
O Allah!
Attack!
I'm here, Osman Bey!
Bala!
Shield wall!
Ya Haqq!
Nayman
Stay together!
Now we're outnumbered, Lord.
I'm not like you, Nayman.
I will not tolerate defeat!
Lord, not now!
We're retreating,
we're drawing back.
O Allah
This is a land of Turks!
Allah is the greatest!
O Allah.
I'm curious about Osman
and the children.
-I can't stand this.
-Malhun Hatun.
If you leave now,
you will risk your life and your child's life.
Have patience for a while longer Malhun.
I know your test is tough.
But Yenisehir is trusted to you.
Think about your child's life, if not yours.
InshaAllah we will receive good news soon.
We have received news,
Osman Bey is all right and they are coming.
-Thankfully.
Thankfully.
Do you see, new sibling is coming,
so they forgot about you just like me.
But don't worry, I'm here.
I will never leave you alone sister.
My Bey, as you ordered, we sent an alp
to inform Yenisehir about the situation.
What about the situation in Konya?
Sultan Mesut did not give up when the troops were hit.
Support unit of Jandarids is coming to the frontiers.
Here, our salvation depends on this unit.
...x 'tJJ
Osman Bey.
Kids, Bala.
People are all right,
thankfully we didn't lose many people.
Here, Bala Hatun. Thank you.
Thankfully.
Thankfully we have repelled this trouble as well.
-Thankfully.
Kids performed a great resistance.
You came right on time, Bala.
But most importantly
Salur Bey and his people.
They fought so hard, we're glad
to have them, may Allah bless them.
May Allah bless you too, Osman Bey.
Our courage derives from you, Osman Bey.
Astagfirullah. Astagfirullah.
Astagfirullah.
While we were wandering idly
to find a land to settle,
...you gave us a home.
You put the da'wah of holy war in our hearts.
It is our duty to be with you
in your hard day, Osman Bey.
No. We gave lands to many...
...but they turned their back on us
in our hardest day.
Do you know what's the real courage, Salur Bey?
The real courage
is the loyalty
that showed in the hard day.
But we have harder days ahead.
We couldn't hit the commanders.
We couldn't stop the army.
We're in a hard spot.
But the greatest healing...
...is our unity.
Here...
...those who didn't even see our faces...
...became shields for us today.
May Allah bless them all.
-Ameen.
As long as you support us...
...we will never be defeated.
-May Allah have our unity last forever.
-Ameen.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Send alps everywhere.
Find out how many people are there in that army,
where will they pass, find out their whole route.
Yes my Bey. Come on brother.
Kids, Bala.
Let us leave.
Thank you for everything.
-Give us your pardon.
-Of course, Osman Bey.
Give us your pardon.
I do.
Come on now.
-Come on.
-Come on kids.
Lord.
Osman's family
they are risking their lives to protect him.
If I didn't have the seal
maybe most of those behind me would try to kill me.
Osman's greatest power is his family.
They all look like they have been captivated.
Soldiers!
Dismount from the horses.
Soldiers and horses
will go to the castle separately.
You will walk!
Yes, mighty Lord.
If I told them to die
they would die, Nayman.
Also I don't have any seal.
If it's out of fear, why would a soldier
who is ready to sacrifice his life be afraid?
If it's loyalty, then be it.
If it's people, then be it.
I'm strong enough to crush Osman under my feet.
And this is just a beginning.
When you see the ones who unite under my banner,
you will see what does it mean to be captivated.
Let the armies come quickly.
We will not be defeated again, Lord!
The army will not come for now.
What do you mean they won't?
First, I want a leading troop
that's made of the strongest ones.
They will be capable of hiding.
Their strength will be equal to a lion's strength.
They will not miss their shoots.
A leading troop that's made of the wildest ones.
What will they do?
You saw the loyalty of
the people who follow Osman.
They will come and they will destroy them.
Their soldiers, their commanders.
Their beys, all of them
They will destroy everyone
who believes in Osman!
Keep your army ready, Nayman.
When it is over
all the rivers will be blood-red.
This time
you will not be able to escape, Osman.
Thanks to Allah.
We are getting over every move of our enemies.
What is your intention now?
You know my intention, my Bala.
My intention is to stab the infidels' heart.
Look, I did not know that.
You say it is a secret, ha?
A secret that you also hide from me.
EyvAllah Osman Bey. EyvAllah.
My Bala.
Our intention is to ruin the dreams of our enemies.
You already know that. Come here. Come.
Good, good. I understood.
Fortunately, we are in a hurry for something good...
...so I am not pushing you about the battle thing.
You say the cloud does not cover the sun anymore.
Hearts must be filled with joy.
Tell me. What is that good news?
They could not say it yet.
-Our Ulgen and..
-Cerkutay?
Come on, Ulgen!
Hang on! Do not die!
Run! Faster!
I am too tired
-I cannot walk!
-Come on! You cannot give up!
You cannot give up! Come on
Len, didn't you just come from the battle?
Go and have some rest!
Why are you having fun with me?
Fighting and battle is a wedding for us!
Can't I make you run because
I fought a little with my swords?
Come on Ulgen
Len
I have no power left! Enough
That's not enough. You cannot give up!
Your mother asked for your weight in gold.
How can I find all that gold, Ulgen?
At least let me eat a piece of bread.
You are making me run but I am starving!
You will not eat!
You will lose weight...
...until I find that gold.
Enough! Enough!
What kind of a stingy man are you?
I'm sorry.
This apple would do no harm.
No! No!
-No! Ulgen...
-Cerkutay!
-Give me my apple back.
-Ulgen...
Once we are married...
I will rain apples on you.
Come on.
Come on Ulgen. Hang on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on
Come on! Hurry!
Well done!
Come on
Well done, Ulgen
-Faster! Go!
-Damn it.
Come on, please! Come on
Come on
Allah..
Come on! Faster!
Allah... Allah..
I'm alright.
Come on! Come on
He is going to starve me to death to give less gold.
Pay it.
Bring us all that gold. I don't care.
I will eat it now.
Don't stop.
Ulgen..
Who is that man working for? For us!
He keeps fighting..
..and never has a rest.
Alps!
No, I won't eat it. I won't eat it.
Marriage is such a hard thing! Off!
Come on! Come on, Ulgen
Come on! Faster!
Run! Run
-I arrived!
-Ulgen
Come on... Ulgen...
Come on, one more time.
Come on! The last time!
Faster!
Where is Cerkutay?
Hasn't he come yet?
He is at the exercising place.
He is with Ulgen Hatun.
May it be good brother.
Did they go to exercise?
Yes. She is exercising.
The Dark Midwife...
...asked for as much gold as
Ulgen Hatun's weight.
He is trying to make her lose weight!
Look, he is coming.
I will not cut it..
I swear it's for a good cause...
Who are you talking to?
-To Gurbuz.
-I wasn't even involved in the conversation!
The name of the goat is Gurbuz.
He really lost his mind.
What did you do?
What can I do?
I found the goat.
Now I will go and talk to the Dark Midwife.
Cerkutay... Brother...
Do you think it is going to
happen with only a goat?
- The Dark Midwife asked many things!
-What can I do?
What can I do? How am I going to do it?
The Dark Midwife
asks for so many things!
What could I do? I did you a favor!
If I hadn't talked to her, you would have
been crying in front of the kitchen.
Cerkutay brother...
What happened?
Couldn't you gather those things?
How could I?
I just found the goat.
Once I get married...
...I will start collecting
the gold and build the house...
The Dark Midwife will never accept that brother.
She won't.
Forget getting married before preparing...
- ...what Dark Midwife asked for, brother.
-Forget it.
How am I going to do it, brother?
I found this goat.
How am I going to build that house?
Say I did it.
How am I going to collect
Ulgen's weight in gold?
Anyway.
I will talk to the Dark Midwife first. Come on.
Come out, Dark Midwife.
Huseyin.
Go and bring me two chests of gold. Come on.
-My Bey..
-Yes?
- Did you say gold?
- Yeah.
Are you sure?
Towba astagfurullah.
Go Huseyin. Go.
-Go.
-My Bey...
It won't come back.
That Cerkutay will never be able to pay it back.
Huseyin! I am still injured and it still hurts!
Do not make me take my revenge from you!
My Bey... Look, I'm going.
Walk before I cut your head off.
You have eyes like a hawk, my Osman.
You deal with traitors inside and outside...
...but you also know the wounds
in your Alps' hearts.
We were also in love.
Were?
-So it is in the past, huh, Osman Bey?
-No.
-Did our love become old?
-No. How can that happen?
Come here.
Just like the very first day...
..still like a knot.
Look at me. Cerkutay, huh?
So it's a good thing.
Let's question him first.
Bride's house is always right.
Right... We are always right.
Right. You made me suffer many times!
-Who's name is it?
-The goat's.
Everyone heard of this goat in Yenisehir.
You can ask around if you want to.
So it's name is Gurbuz.
Good, good.
Where are the others?
Dark Midwife...
About that..
The others..
-After the council, I will..
-No way.
Are you trying to trick me, lunatic boy?
Dark Midwife.
Let us find a way.
Let's half the gold business.
Sure, so that Cerkutay won't be in debt.
No way.
Do I want these golds for myself?
I want it for my daughter.
Dark Midwife.
Don't you worry about this gold business.
It is alright.
I had a debt for my brother Cerkutay for a while.
It is time to pay.
Leave it near Gurbuz.
Half of it is council gift.
And the other is valiant Cerkutay's.
Bayindir Bey.
MashAllah.
The gold business is done.
Now, find a house..
And come take my daughter.
Cerkutay.
Bey.
What is happening here?
What is happening
Bey, I...I..
I was going to inform you..
However, you were..
Quite busy..
Stop it, stop it.
Look at me.
You want a girl.. In my mansion..
In my house..
Without asking me?
Forgive me Bey.
Tell me.
Dark Midwife.
No Bey, he hasn't yet.
He is just wandering around here.
Bey, I haven't yet.
Cerkutay.
-You didn't give her to him right?
-No, Bey.
She didn't.
What do you want?
Bey, I wanted gold and he provided.
I wanted goat, and he provided as well.
And I want a house for them to stay.
The house is done.
Let's get her.
Now, Bey?
Now, now.
Good business like this should be made hastily.
Bey.
-Cerkutay.
-Bey.
And this was a business
that should've been dealt with for a while.
And Osman Bey likes to
rush the good business like this.
I do indeed.
Come on then.
Let us assemble the council.
Alps, begin preparations.
Valens' savages..
They will kill everyone
who supports Osman.
They will kill Osman's commanders.
However, the real war is different.
My army will prepare for it.
We will be together..
With the upcoming army of Valens..
The armies will unite.
There will be two mountains.
And Osman will be crushed
between those two mountains.
I will destroy all Osman's lands.
And in the end, Konya.
Are you afraid?
I am not, Grand Commander Nayman.
The death is far from us when
under your service.
Those who will die are different.
Konya, Yenisehir, Sogut..
All Turkmens..
Will be destroyed..
When my army unites with Lord's.
Tendu, train the nokers well.
My army will be very strong..
In the grand war.
Quickly.
Here are our golds.
The house is a promise of mine.
Alps will build a great house for them..
At the most beautiful place in Yenisehir.
InshAllah.
Until then, they will live in the mansion.
And our goat is here.
To cut it shortly..
With the command of Allah,
with the words of the prophet..
We want our girl Ulgen..
To my alp Cerkutay.
Ulgen.
Do you have consent to this?
Yes, mother.
Then..
They fell in love.
Our respect to love is infinite.
I know Cerkutay,
I've observed him since I came here.
He is a man of his words.
However, Cerkutay..
You will give me a promise.
You will take..
Good care of my daughter.
You can trust me.
Congratulations, brother.
Ulgen.
It is hard to be a wife of an alp.
Do you have consent to this burden?
am, mother.
Good.
I trust you with Cerkutay as well.
You will take good care of him.
I will, mother.
Congratulations.
Then, I'll allow it.
Let it be mubarak.
-Praise be!
-Congratulations.
We have council this night.
May the preparations begin quickly.
Osman Bey, how will this happen
with all these dangers going on?
And we don't know what Lord Valens will do.
That's how it is in these lands, Eskigun.
Our weddings, our celebrations..
Are all done while fighting with infidels.
And, fighting is wedding to a Turk.
Cerkutay.
Brother..
My Commanders...
You..
...will welcome the vanguards
that will arrive in KartalGozu.
This vanguard..
...has the strongest soldiers you can ever see.
Each one is wilder than the other.
Those who were created to fight.
Osman..
..tried to..
..kill you..
...my commanders and my consul brothers.
The main purpose of this incoming vanguard...
...will be to destroy Osman's commanders...
...and Beys.
Osman must have taken a precaution against this.
He knows that an army is coming.
No doubt.
He must be waiting for us
like a deer with its ears pricked up.
He built a wall of flesh everywhere...
..for his dear folk.
But he doesn't know..
...that those who come are the biggest of the hunters.
Osman will do his best to
prevent this vanguard from coming.
What is our duty, Valens?
We will not make a mistake and underestimate Osman.
We will ensure that
the vanguard arrives safely on our lands.
They will come..
...and I will make them die the worst way.
Sir.. Forgive me, but there is important news.
They encountered Osman' Alps around KartalGozu.
They ran away.
As you can see..
...Osman never stops!
He is watching us like a deer trying to see the hunter!
My Cerkutay...
Are you excited because of the wedding, brother?
Yes, brother.
We could not shoot the Commanders
or the consul...
...and the army is at the door
on western front.
Why are you worried about that, Cerkutay?
Didn't my Bey say that it works like that in here?
Infidels and ceremonies will always be here.
Cerkutay...
...don't you hear your Bey, huh?
Or is it a gift for you not to hear?
No way, my Bey.
During these hard days... I rushed.
-The army is at the door.
-Stop there.
Stop. Konur is right.
We can fight and organize a wedding
Let's hold that wedding first.
Don't worry.
Alps are watching the way anyway.
My Bey, can I come in?
Come in Samil.
My Bey. We received news from our watchmen.
The armies stopped. But a vanguard is setting out.
Alps seemed bad when talking about the vanguard, my Bey.
They say they are the most talented warriors of west.
One of them worths ten men. Their armous...
...their swords, their talents are all special.
Special huh? Then..
...we will bury them in the most beautiful...
...place of our land with our special swords.
So that they are coming..
...then they will learn a lesson.
Now..
...where will the army come from?
Where will it stop? Where will it settle?
You will know all of them.
-Yes my Bey.
-My Bey...
-This is not about today.
We will take our precaution and continue.
Don't worry.
Here..
This is my wedding gift for you.
My Bey...
-My Bey, thank you.
-Cerkutay... Cerkutay...
Come on now. The bride's house always says no first.
But groom's house is always ready.
Come on now. There is a ceremony to attend.
Lords!
This isn't a game, but a war!
And I'll decide who will win and lose!
Osman knows about the vanguard!
And he will do his best to stop them.
If the vanguard is strong as you said,
...you shouldn't be afraid. They won't fail.
They may not.
Then what are you for, Lord?
I'd rather go back to my castle and take measures.
Are you afraid of a wounded wolf?
I don't like cowards.
We're the ones to choke him.
The vanguard..
...will use the route that we all know well.
So everyone will stay here.
We will talk.
If Osman is watching us instead of taking measures,
...then we can choose what he's going to see.
You're tired. Get some rest.
By the morning, I'll have drawn the picture
that Osman is going to see.
Have a nice rest.
I said have a nice rest!
Look at the bride.
She has henna on her hands.
Don't say anything to the bride.
She may take offense and go back home.
Her door is hennaed.
She has an angel-like nature.
May your bride-henna be holy.
May you be happy in your tent.
Look at the bride.
She has henna on her hands.
Don't say anything to the bride.
She may take offense and go back home.
Her door is hennaed.
She has an angel-like nature.
May your bride-henna be holy.
May you be happy in your tent.
-May Allah bless it.
-Thanks.
May Allah give you a bright future.
Amen, mother.
-Amen.
My beauty, let's apply henna on you too.
You should. She's a big sister now.
I don't want. I'm just Halime's sister.
I won't sister anyone else.
Why is that, Fatma?
If I sister someone else, my sister will be upset.
Fatma, are you afraid that you will lose favor?
You should be.
Another baby is coming.
Both you and Halime will lose favor.
Not at all.
Come on, hatuns.
They're waiting for us. Let's go.
-Do you?
-I do.
Do you?
I do.
Ulgen Hatun. Do you take...
...Cerkutay to be your husband?
I do.
-Do you?
-I do.
Witnesses.
Do you witness?
We do.
-May Allah bless your marriage.
-Amen!
We seek refuge in Allah from the accursed Satan.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
-Come on then
-In the name of Allah.
-Brother.
-My Bey.
Congratulations.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks, my Bey.
We gave a girl to a Mongolian.
Now it's time to take a girl
from a Mongolian.
Right, Esrigun Hatun?
Do you have someone in your heart?
No, Dark Midwife.
I have nothing else but my sword in my heart.
You will.
You can never be sure about heart affairs.
Right, Boran Alp?
Alps!
Now it's your turn
I'll keep an eye on you.
No more single days!
I will make you all get married
Do I have permission, Osman Bey?
You have it.
We're ready to have the wedding whenever you like.
Osman Bey.
It's Bayindir Bey's turn.
No way
It's brother Boran's turn
Not at all, Bayindir Bey.
It's brother Onur's turn.
Stop fighting
I will make everyone of you get married!
Alps!
Draw your swords!
-As my Bey orders!
-As you order, my Bey!
-Cheer it up!
Come on, brothers!
What did Cerkutay Alp do?
He ate, he drank and he fought.
What did he do for Ulgen Hatun?
He brought the biggest goat of Yenisehir.
What else did he do?
He ate foods, he made her eat and drink.
He brought gold equal to her weight!
And he was beaten by a stick.
Commander Nayman is sleeping,
go back to your duties.
The one who tries to kill Nayman
who was blessed by Gok Teng
will suffer the wrath of Erlik Han.
Esrigun sent you.
You will be her death warrant.
Forgive me, forgive me great Nayman.
My spy Ayceren is the closest one to Nayman.
I will take the seal.
Nayman cannot do anything without the seal.
He can only wait for the day
that he will lose his head.
Esrigun Hatun.
-Do you think she can handle it?
-She will.
Otherwise it will be too hard for us to defeat Nayman.
-When will she bring the seal?
-She'll bring it tomorrow, InshaAllah.
EyvAllah. EyvAllah.
But it is dangerous.
You are Gazan Khan's trust to us.
We cannot let you go alone.
Boran is my right hand man.
She will be with you in this case.
I can handle it alone, Osman Bey.
-Thank you.
-For you to survive
Boran will be with you in this case.
Yes my Bey.
I'll keep an eye on your trust, my Bey.
My Sultans are here.
Come here now, come here.
If you'll excuse me, Osman Bey.
Of course.
Boran.
Come here now.
Father, don't you miss us?
Of course I do.
I feel pain at the tip of my nose
whenever I don't see you.
You say so, but you always take
my brothers to the battle.
You don't take us at all.
My beautiful daughter, look Halime cannot walk yet.
So you need to help her, take care of her.
Let's do it that way for now. But,
if you don't take us there when
my sister grows up, you'll see the consequences.
Don't you worry.
Just grow up
then you will go everywhere I go.
Father, everyone says something about my shoes
-They say that...
-Fatma.
My beautiful daughter, your father needs to work.
Come on, let's put Halime to sleep.
I'll take her to the bed, no one but her can understand me now.
Of course not, where are you leaving?
Hang on.
No one can rule you out.
Let me tell you a tale.
My sweethearts.
There are those
who would die for their loved ones.
Ulgen.
My Ulgen.
There are those...
...who would die for their loved ones.
-He goes...
-I said my Ulgen!
Cerkutay?
Ulgen.
Ulgen, I understand you.
But stop. You'll be chocked up.
Nothing will happen. I'll eat it.
-Wait, Ulgen.
Wait, you'll be chocked up.
Ulgen stop, Ulgen stop.
Look at them.
Will you eat them all?
You ate your share. These are mine.
-All of them?
-All of them!
You heard about the gold equal to my weight,
you didn't let me eat anything.
These are mine now.
You were so hungry, is that so?
You left me hungry.
For the sake of gold,
you left me hungry,
don't you feel any guilt?
-Ulgen, don't.
-I'll do so.
-Cerkutay!
-You'll blow up!
I'm saying for your own sake.
No eating, give it to me.
Ulgen, give it to me. That's enough!
-No.
-Did I do this to you?
Do you make my daughter starve on the first day?
No, no mother.
No mother. How could that be.
Mother, stop
-It's not like that.
-What? I heard it all.
Mother, don't be mad,
Cerkutay looks after me well.
-You sure?
-I am sure.
Look at me, if he acts bad to you..
-Mother.
-Mother, what are you saying?
I look after my Ulgen well.
Even..
I brought him flow..
Lan! (Turkish slang word for"son!")
Lunatic Boy!
Do you bring grass to my daughter?
Do you make fun of my daughter?
Lan Gurbuz!
What did you do to the flowers?
Let it go, its not his fault.
Come my Gurbuz.
My goat, my Gurbuz.
My Gurbuz.
Lan Gurbuz..
Ah, Gurbuz..
Quickly now brother, quickly.
I came to pick you up.
I was not talking about you,
I was talking about Gurbuz.
What are you saying?
Cerkutay, Osman Bey is about to be here!
Quickly, to Sogut, follow me.
All Gurbuzs are the same.
I am leaving now.
However, you should know that..
I will not die from a sword wound
I will die from your mother's staff.
She can kill for sure.
Her staff is very popular
around the whole world.
Look here, I did not tell my mother.
Thus saving you from a head wound.
From now on, I am the most precious.
Am I full?
I am not full.
-Peace be upon you, brothers.
-Peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you too.
Beys have arrived at Sogut,
they wait for Osman Bey.
Let's be ready quickly, brothers.
Sahin..
When will the scouts allow for taking land?
The scouts are after it, brother.
We will learn, inshAllah.
Now, the important thing
is not when they will arrive.
It is how Osman Bey will stop them.
My Bey promise them a place beneath the dirt.
-You are right.
-He must have a move.
So that's why all those Beys gathered in Sogut.
We will soon learn about our goal.
Until then, we need to wait patiently.
-Yes brother.
Quickly, Bey is waiting for us.
Don't do this Grand Commander Nayman.
If you let me go, if you show mercy..
Ghazan Khan will forgive you.
-Where did you find it?
-I find it on her.
The map of their meeting place.
All of the places, except one.
Ayceren... Esrigul...
While your owner is waiting to get the seal..
He will lose his life.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
May Allah's blessing upon you.
Look sister, now they are after our shoes.
They will throw our shoes
to do roof, or they say.
I will not allow it of course. Look,
I carry them with me.
Now, I will teach them such a lesson that..
They will love us the most.
And those babies will see!
I did it before and it worked.
Now I will do it again.
Come on sister, let's go to our tribe.
Parents are at council, no one can see us.
Don't you cry though.
Come on.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
You may sit.
I am opening the council..
In the name of Allah and
His ninety nine names..
Making us responsible for not victory..
But the campaign.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Lord Valens.
We couldn't stop the army
he sent from the west...
...to raid our lands.
We were in a hard position.
But..
...we have never been worried.
Why?
Because there are brave men like Salur Bey.
We thank him. He opened his door to us.
He shed his blood.
He stood behind us
to his last breath.
Thank you.
You proved your capabilities.
From now on
you'll always have a place in my council.
The heart of people like you
always makes us hopeful.
Osman Bey.
Your da'wah of holy war is in our heart.
Alp, bring it here.
Salur Bey, here.
From now on
you'll always have a right to talk in my council.
May Allah bless you my Bey.
EyvAllah. EyvAllah.
The army headed towards us
has stopped before entering our lands.
What is their intention, my Bey?
Their intention is to break us.
Just like we tried to hit their commanders
they will want to do the same to us.
How do we know that, my Bey?
You, me
the competent warriors,
how can they disperse our army
before hitting us and other beys.
How can they raid these lands?
So the competent troop
will want to do this first.
Osman Bey.
Don't worry at all.
No one in this council
is afraid of death at all.
All right then.
Whatever their move is
our conquests will never stop.
No matter what their intentions are...
...they will never be able to come closer
to our dreams and our goals.
You may leave now.
Since you're watching us,
since you want to hit
I set up a great game for you Osman.
Come here
...and let me show you the picture
that Osman will see.
Armies will split into three here.
There are already a few men
and splitting them into three...
However!
The chosen ones will only be the number one..
..among these troops.
The other two are baits.
To split Osman into three and destroy them.
Will we use our soldiers as baits?
They are
Muslim hostages that were weaponized.
What if Osman
makes a move to destroy all three of them.
Let him do it.
Then he will die.
Because the chosen ones
are way more crowded than they seem.
If Osman
i c i
attacks the right way.
He will die.
<0
If he attacks the wrong way
the chosen ones will enter his lands,
and they'll destroy them all.
So,
we will be the victorious side
in both of these options.
Byzantium
should not be worried.
Osman, who dreams about conquests,
will die today.
Our conquests will never stop.
Our eyes have always been on Kestel,
Lefke and Koyunhisar.
But from now on, not only our eyes,
our swords will be there too.
Uraz Bey.
You'll have the Kestel Castle.
It will be a big siege.
Yes my Bey.
Demirhan Bey.
You'll have the Lefke Citadel.
Yes my bey.
When it conies to you, Salur Bey.
You'll deal with Gemlik.
Yes my Bey.
Osman Bey, forgive me but,
what is my duty?
You will be with me.
You will be with me from now on.
My Bey, the murderers of Lord Valens,
if we don't hit them, walking towards
conquests while the beys are on target...
The dogs bark, but the caravan goes on, Cerkutay.
We will not stop.
If we stop, then we will lose.
We will keep going.
Alps are watching the paths,
let us learn their move.
We will counteract even harder.
InshaAllah we will not let them
open their eyes my Bey.
EvelAllah.
May I come in my Bey?
Come on in.
My Bey, scouts watching the armies
have sent a message.
Lord dispersed the vanguard.
They're advancing in three separate ways cautiously.
Lord..
He wants to divide us into three.
Tell me. Which routes are they using?
My Bey, the first one is here.
The woods behind Kestel.
The other troop are going
along the river through the Gemlik road.
And the last one..
...is going along the mountain behind Iznik.
You mean here.
Here.
Lords..
They forgot how to read
the nature as they stayed in castles.
Now tell me. Which way..
...will the best troop take?
Riverside is where they can advance fastest.
They can reach Bursa...
...and the frontiers quickly.
Kestel woods will hide them, my Bey.
If they want to arrive safely,
...they will take that way.
You say mountains are only for goats.
Why would soldiers take that way, huh?
If the best troop want to hit us,
...they will definitely take that route.
The mountains of Iznik..
...will be where the best troop is.
-Can I, my Bey?
-Come in!
My Bey, we got a message from Constantinople.
EyvAllah.
Martalaus who is in Constantinople...
...mentions the same route.
The best troop is...
...going to pass here.
What are your orders, my Bey?
We've found out their routes.
Now we will show them our hospitality.
We'll let them listen to songs of our swords.
Now we will hit them hard.
Everyone on horses!
We're close.
Don't be afraid, Esrigun Hatun.
We'll find your spy alive, InshaAllah.
What would I be afraid of?
Well, heathens keep following us.
What would you do here alone without me?
My strength fears the enemy, Boran Alp.
I would manage without you.
EyvAllah.
Why are you carrying that?
After the last ambush we fell into
...I decided to keep it with me.
It knows Yenisehir and the mansion well.
And I'm supposed to protect you.
That's why I'm so cautious.
This is it.
Ayceren must have arrived by now.
Ayceren
-Ayceren!
-Be careful.
Ayceren?
Come on, come on
I was waiting for you, Esrigun
Your spy died in my hands!
I will take your breath away!
While you carry your head over your shoulders,
...I won't die but kill, Nayman
Attack!
You said your sword was solid.
Let's see if it is true.
You will see.
Ya Haqq!
Selamun aleykum.
Aleykum selam, valiants.
These are the last ones, Kumral Abdal.
What bothers you?
More than half of the sack
is full of stones, Kumral Abdal.
Fortunately, we looked in them at the shop...
...we took care of the issue.
But we were very upset.
My father works hard
and makes an effort for his people.
He always fights.
Look at what the traders are doing.
We dream of establishing a state.
Are we going to establish the state with these people?
Yes we are.
And no matter how hard you try to pick...
...stones will always be mixed with the wheat.
But we will always pick those stones.
Come on valiants.
Take these bags.
Two handfuls of wheat in each bag.
Time belongs to Allah, my Orhan.
People also belong to Allah.
But you should know..
...nothing happens because of time.
Just as the water of one mountain..
...resembles the water of another mountain..
...people are similar to each other...
...no matter what period they live in.
Think of Kabil.
When he was presenting his goods..
..he chose the worst ones.
But Habil..
..chose the best ones.
And it is the same now.
There is Kabil and Habil.
You are right, Kumral Abdal.
But still, I cannot stand it.
Sure you cannot.
We may not be able to stand it.
Wherever there is a mistake..
..something contrary to the will of Allah...
...we will correct it with our hands.
If we can't do it with our hands,
...we should do it by our tongues.
If our tongues aren't enough
..then..
...we should stand against that evil thing in our hearts.
Thanks to Allah, our hands were enough, Kumral Abdal.
What are these pouches for?
For what our hands are enough for.
Just like Hadhrat Omer (R.A) didn't let birds starve,
...Osman Bey won't either.
We prepared sacks for them.
We'll establish the state that we have been dreaming for.
We'll establish the state where we even provide for...
...even the birds and bugs in mountains.
We will.
Come on, boys. Come on.
Birds and bugs in mountains are hungry! Come on!
Hold this.
Wait, sister.
Fatma
Fatma?
Halime?
What are you doing here?
You've started walking?
No way.
Fatma
You must have done this, Fatma.
Malhun Hatun! Malhun Hatun!
Malhun Hatun
-What's the matter?
-Boran Alp.
-He got ambushed.
-Ambushed?
Give it to me.
Boran.
Alps, prepare the horses!
Bring the swords! Come on!
Malhun Hatun, you can't ride.
-For your baby.
-I have to.
They are in danger. We can't be late.
If you ride, I can't save the baby.
Malhun.
You come by the carriage.
I go ahead and let Bala know, alright?
Come on then.
Ulgen, take care of Fatma and Halime.
Well... Where is Fatma?
Fatma
Come! I will make cookies for you!
Boran.
I'm good.
Go into the woods. I will follow you. Go!
I'm not someone who leaves fellows behind.
We'll get out together or we won't.
Boran.
We're coming Boran
MashaAllah.
Come on, come on! Come on!
Allah is the greatest!
Alps, attack!
Allah is Hayy!
Allah is the greatest!
Ambush
Come on brothers!
Allah is the greatest!
We're drawing back!
-O Haqq!
Welcome to the land of Turks.
We were coming to you Osman.
We have come here so that you do not get tired.
After we kill your commanders and beys,
it was going to be your turn.
-You made it easy for us by coming early.
-Right.
That's what our religion orders us to do.
It says "do not make it hard...
...make it easier."
And..
Here, with our alps..
we are to make it easier for you.
So that's what it is.
The field is ours!
-O Allah!
-You will die in this field, Osman!
Allah is the greatest!
We will be the doom of infidels!
We will dig their graves!
Allah is the greatest!
Mother.
Fatma.
My daughter!
I wanted only one.
You came with ten.
Osman.
Your heart is in my hands.
Alp..
Mother.
I will get your heart, Osman.
Fatma run
-Fatma run! Run!
-Mother.
Aktemur!
Cerkutay.
How could this happen?
My Bey.
Allah is the greatest!
We will take a thousand lives for one life.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com